Dreaded by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
So, you finally made it here. Once you do, you've got the nerve to attack our guys. I'm gonna need an explanation for that.
Yami was under attack by two elves who had possessed the bodies of Marks and Owen.
Memory magic! Torment's Canceller attack!
He just managed to fend them off.
What? Red roses.
When a mysterious and powerful elf resembling Charlotte Roselay appeared on the sea.
I don't know you at all. You seem capable for a human.
I don't know you.
Thank you.
だから待って待って待って待って置いてかないでてよ
今すぐfly away戦うtry again
だから待って待って待って同じ場所にいたいよ
霞が痛い胸の痛みが君に話したい僕の気持ちが本当のことね
there
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
There.
It should be safe now.
That black bull.
He acted like it was important.
What did he say was inside?
Dark magic.
Dark cloak dimension.
Flash.
Crimson guy.
Fear.
Oh, no.
We cast our spells at the same time.
Mine was clearly the more devastating one.
Yet his attack split it in two, which slowed down its momentum and prevented the town from being completely decimated by the impact.
Even if it just hit my gauntlet, his spell had enough force left to reach me.
Despite the difference in our might, he was able to turn the tide of battle in his favor.
How could a lowly human have achieved this level of mastery?
Though I suppose he must be exceptional if he beat those two.
It seems I underestimated humankind.
I used more magic than planned, so I'll retreat.
It's best to wait for Licht and the others to arrive so that I can ensure their safety.
Char!
What about the captain of the Black Bulls?
What the?
No!
Did Char crush him?
She wouldn't.
Don't run away from me, woman!
I still got a bone to pick with you, you hear?
I could've died from a stunt like that!
Where is she?
You're alive!
I mean, whatever.
I guess that's a good thing.
As soon as I snap you out of this little mean streak of yours, I'm gonna make you pay big for that!
You're not getting off the hook!
Oh, it's Tomboy.
What did you just call me?
Why are you still here?
What about the thing I gave you?
I hid it in a safe place.
Oh, that's real reassuring.
You know I'm trusting you, right?
Well, back at ya!
I trusted you to save Char!
Who do you think I am?
I can't help her the way I am now.
Look, I trust you!
Wouldn't care if you didn't.
So?
What's the next step?
I'm trying to figure that out.
Alright?
I got it!
You go take care of the townspeople!
I'm sure there's more magic knights here.
Find them and help everyone you can!
Right!
As for my part...
Well...
What happened here?
I haven't a clue what the commotion is outside, but I am detecting a colossal amount of
magic power.
Apparently enough to destroy the seal on this prison.
Whatever the cause may be, it looks like today's my lucky day.
Now I'll finally be able to escape.
Hmm.
Well, of all the degenerates I could have run into down here...
Hello, Captain Gelder.
I'm sorry.
Ex-Captain.
Believe me, I'm just as surprised as you are.
I thought for certain I had seen the last of Chain Magic Rev Chiefs.
How long has it been?
Unfortunately, I'm in quite a hurry.
So we'll have to reserve the last of Chain Magic Rev Chiefs.
I'm sure I'm in a hurry.
I'll be able to save the last of Chain Magic Rev Chiefs.
Whatever the cause may be, it looks like today's my lucky day.
Now I'll finally be able to escape.
Hmm.
Well, of all the degenerates I could have run into down here...
Hello, Captain Gelder.
I'm sorry.
Ex-Captain.
Believe me, I'm just as surprised as you are.
I thought for certain I had seen the last of Chain Magic Rev Chiefs.
How long has it been?
Unfortunately, I'm in quite a hurry.
So we'll have to reserve the reminiscing for another time.
That might be more convenient for you, but I'm afraid it simply isn't going to work for me.
As you may recall, sir, two years ago, you sent me on the assignment that left me with this unsightly scar.
And after the mission resulted in failure, you placed the blame on me and my status as member of the Purple Orcus was permanently revoked.
Oh, is that it?
It serves you right that you were banished.
I believe your squad mates weren't terribly fond of you anyway.
Not a single one of them was willing to take your side if I remember correctly.
Isn't that rich?
Seems like you aren't very popular either.
Why else would the previous Captain of the Purple Orcas have been locked away to rot down here in this underground prison?
You have no right to judge the behavior of a Captain seeing as how you were always perfectly content to let everyone around you move up in rank while you consistently dodged any mission that appeared to be even remotely dangerous.
You shouldn't accuse me of dodging when your transparency magic is nothing but dodging.
It's far better than your cowardly chain magic, sealing the power of any mage you meet so that you don't have to fight.
If it weren't for that infinite little upstart and his anti-magic abilities, there wouldn't be anyone in Clover Kingdom who could stand in my way!
Huh?
What, you two?
It seems we feel the same.
His magic power is enormous!
I can tell that without using my chains!
There are humans here as well.
Is he one of the people destroying the city?
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is behind all this chaos?
If so, it seems I may have gotten myself involved with a rather deadly organization.
We've been instructed to massacre any humans we see.
All of you!
Wait!
I assure you I am not your enemy!
In fact, I may even be able to aid your endeavor!
Please, let me speak with your leader!
We refuse to be fooled by you wicked humans again!
You all die!
Everyone, no matter who you are!
Oh?
We all die?
I suppose we have no other choice then, Rep Chief.
It kills me to say this, but you're right.
If he's threatening our lives, there's only one thing to do.
Transparency magic!
Invisible Seeker plus Invisible Traveling Companion!
They're gone!
And their magic power disappeared with them?
In that case, I'll tear apart this whole area!
Chain Creation Magic!
Magic Finding Iron Chain Formation!
Did he just seal away my magic power?
Impossible!
My strength is far superior to theirs!
What kind of techniques are those?
Now that he's taken care of, we should be home free!
Finally, these poor eyes of mine will see the light of day once more!
Indeed!
I knew it wasn't my fate to die in here!
Rev G, let us make haste to clear our sullied names once and for all!
Excellent idea!
Good idea!
You guys!
What's wrong?
It's just like with Veto and the others.
It feels so evil!
Why's that kind of magic power coming from you?
Noelle's right.
There's something terribly malicious at play here.
Much like that House Vaud fellow.
An ominous aura indeed.
Finally, we've made it back.
Let me kill them.
Hmph.
You're energetic considering you've just awakened.
Yeah, that's why I'm so pumped.
Extra pumped actually.
Oh dear.
This thing is in the way.
Luck?
I don't get it.
What are you...
Uh, I was hoping they'd be a challenge, but they are human.
I missed ya.
Looks like I've gotten a little rusty.
Let's try again.
Cherry blossom magic!
Raging magic!
Cherry blossom!
Storm of petals!
I don't know what caused this change in them.
But they certainly aren't the people they were before.
You should prepare yourself to fight beautifully, Noelle.
But...
It's Luck!
He's a member of the Black Bulls!
He's my friend!
Noelle!
Hmm...
I can't see.
Which means there's no point in trying to aim.
That's okay.
Hmm...
I'll try plan B.
His strength is growing!
Use a defensive spell!
Fly Luck!
Stop this!
We're friends!
Water creation magic!
See Dragon Slayer!
Noelle-
No!
No, even the essence of their powers changed.
Flux fighting on a totally different level now.
Your spells have a certain feel to them.
Let me guess, your royalty?
You don't...
What if we said yes?
Would you treat my lovely self differently then?
I knew it.
This fight is getting better by the second.
Is this guy pulling my leg or what?
He was overpowered from the beginning.
But now it feels like he's about to blow the roof off.
Like I said, deception is kind of my thing.
And since I'm a liar, I can tell when other people are lying too.
Look, Mr. Anti-Magic.
What you said a little while ago?
I just want a kingdom where all of us get along and laugh together.
And when I'm the Wizard King, we'll have one.
You'll see.
I know you meant every word.
Too bad, really.
For a split second, I was actually moved.
Just like the last time.
Let's foster understanding.
There were no lies in anything that he said.
And so I trusted him.
And what did it get me?
That.
So you see, I'm done with trusting.
And to make sure you know I mean it, I'll kill you.
Copy Light Magic.
Light Swords of Conviction.
Copy Dark Magic.
Lightless Slash.
Two different techniques at the same time?
Mono Zone.
Collidos Brachium.
Bronsbound.
Do you see what I'm saying now?
To them, there is no getting along, no matter how badly you want it.
They're determined to kill every one of us and wipe out all of Clover Kingdom.
Maybe they are.
But I'll still win!
And I'll make a way for us to get along!
The road to mutual understandings closed, pal.
I don't care.
I'll open it back up.
Fine, fine.
You can try.
But you'd better make it quick.
Otherwise, I'll kill him myself.
Right.
Now, Collidos Brachium!
If she manages to hit me with that move of hers,
there's no way I'm going to make it out of this place with my life.
I better be on my toes.
A combination of spatial and light magic.
He's using my light spell to make himself more agile.
Volte's spatial magic is the perfect thing to keep her from hitting me with that attack.
It's sad the old codger's not around anymore,
but at least I got something good out of him.
Copy spatial magic myriad black!
Copy light magic sky-rending flash!
You can't toss forever!
Seriously, this jerk is untouchable!
Will?
Is that you?
Hey, Raya!
Good to see you!
I'm so happy that you're awake!
Hey, Lyra.
You're just as hyperactive as I remember.
Why wouldn't I be?
And you've still got that goofy, spaced-out look on your face.
Can it, kid?
Oh, Raya!
I missed you so much!
Did you stop being a little pain already?
I'm just really happy!
Well, go be happy over there.
Hey!
Will!
Why are you hugging that monster?
You know what?
My ability has a fancy name now.
Picture magic!
Nice.
You do know he's trying to murder us all, right?
Or did you forget?
Say what?
I'm confused.
You are?
We were in the middle of a fight,
and suddenly you bust in,
and you guys are all buddy-buddy?
Do I know you?
What the...
Rill?
Who's Rill?
Didn't you hear?
My name's Lyra.
Huh?
What's going on?
The captain of the Aqua Deer.
His magic power's gone from crazy to ludicrous.
Just like Mr. Copycat over there.
That spatial mage from the Golden Dawn
has felt the same way.
Was that an omen?
Whatever this is,
it must have boosted their strength.
I can tell from the change in their auras
that it's not brainwashing.
That little one doesn't recognize the rookie at all anymore.
Are they being possessed by other people?
It's me, your old friend, Asta.
You and I are both magic knights, remember?
How could you possibly forget about a big loud mouth like me?
Yeah, you're loud and super annoying.
And there's no way I would ever have a human as a friend.
I know how to shut you up.
Check out this picture magic technique.
Four-headed lindworm.
You're no match for me!
He's obviously being controlled by some enemy spell.
You should try smacking him with your anti-magic sword.
Right!
I'm on it!
Sorry, guys.
You can throw whatever you want at us,
but it's never gonna reach us now.
We'll see about that.
You think I've been standing here
twiddling my thumbs this whole time?
Ash-trap magic!
Activate!
Oh, I see.
You were setting something up for us, too, huh?
Big deal.
A paralyzing trap isn't gonna help you much.
I can't see.
But we're good at picking up on other people's powers,
so I'm sure we can still wipe the floor with you guys either way!
Let's see if you feel that way
after this one gets through with you.
He's a magicless monster.
He's got anti-magic coursing through his whole body.
Hey, where are you?
Now step out of it, Will!
Graved him.
It's not much, but it should be enough to break the...
That hurt me, you know.
What's your problem?
It's no good.
Man, I thought for sure that would work.
Sorry, but thanks to reincarnation magic,
we elves have been awakened in these human forms.
Isn't that something?
Whether you understand it or not,
the soul-transferring process is complete,
which means that these bodies belong to us now.
Reincarnation?
Elves?
Quit messing around!
Spring real back!
All of them, too?
This is bad.
Every one of them's given off crazy amounts of power.
We won't last five minutes against them.
Time to go.
Come on.
Do you want to run?
Really?
We can't just leave them.
No way!
Not yet!
Moron.
There's nothing we can do to save them right now.
That's why we should retreat and come up with a plan, birdbrained shorty.
Yeah, you're right.
You and your dumb cool mask.
What's the alternative?
I know you.
And you can't kill your buddies.
Neither can you.
But you can't get away, either.
So you two wimps are out of options.
This is pitiful.
Run along home now, children.
But, Captain!
Captain!
Ah, so you want to stay here and slow us down so they can run back with their tails between their legs.
You seem like a benevolent leader, Madam Royal.
Fool.
You don't understand a thing, do you?
Hmm?
I sent those novices home because they were getting in my way.
Slow you down.
Don't make me laugh.
I wanted the chance to obliterate all of you personally!
Listen to me.
I'm not
I don't need no money, I don't need no魔力は要らない
自力で挑んでミラクル起きること願い
魅力ながら1mmずつビリビリ切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
My disability is my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって
負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に 傷つく音に
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく
Our treasure
裏切らないのは最高にThere is love
Kazashita chinkai hikari ga nikiru treasure